{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"935/55",
			"answer":"935/55",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"640/80",
			"answer":"640/80",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"476/68",
			"answer":"476/68",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"220/44",
			"answer":"220/44",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"672/21",
			"answer":"672/21",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"64/32",
			"answer":"64/32",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"533/41",
			"answer":"533/41",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"882/98",
			"answer":"882/98",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"192/96",
			"answer":"192/96",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"576/64",
			"answer":"576/64",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3.258/0.008",
			"answer":"3.258/0.008",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"58.59/0.7",
			"answer":"58.59/0.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.9919/0.07",
			"answer":"0.9919/0.07",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"176.4/0.2",
			"answer":"176.4/0.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2.404/0.02",
			"answer":"2.404/0.02",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"32.35/0.5",
			"answer":"32.35/0.5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4.22/0.2",
			"answer":"4.22/0.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"71.6/0.04",
			"answer":"71.6/0.04",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.5752/0.08",
			"answer":"0.5752/0.08",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"89.67/0.7",
			"answer":"89.67/0.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}